Boris Ivanov

Shtip, Eastern, North Macedonia



ivanovboris310@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/boris-ivanov-358626279

Summary

I am a Senior Full-Stack Engineer with 7 years of experience in designing, developing, maintaining web applications and integrating 3rd party Web APIs. I have deep knowledge in utilizing React.js/Redux, Next.js, Golang, PHP Laravel and Python. I'm passionate about working with highly skilled teammates, learning new technologies and achieving goals.

I'm here to help you with building your web applications and good relationships, so let us discuss and move forward!

Experience



Senior Full Stack Developer

PropertyRadar

Jan 2022 - Apr 2023 (1 year 4 months)



Senior Backend Developer

callstats.io

May 2020 - Sep 2021 (1 year 5 months)



Full Stack Developer

Invitae

Jan 2019 - Mar 2020 (1 year 3 months)

Frontend Developer

TRINITY MEDIA LLC

Jan 2017 - Oct 2018 (1 year 10 months)

Education



⋒ Ss. Cyril and Methodius University in Skopje / Универзитет "Св. Кирил и Методиј" во Скопје

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science 2012 - 2016

Skills

Next.js • TypeScript • Smart Contracts • Full-Stack Development • Back-End Web Development • Application Programming Interfaces (API) · Code Review · Node.js · Git · GitHub